Mukti used to have a shirt in her childhood on
which was written 'One Two Ka Four Four Two
Ka One'.  He is a fan of Anil Sir since childhood.   Did you
ever think that you would come together, that is, with Anil Sir,
on our show?   not at all.
And I
will do my first movie with him.  This is my debut film.
And I mean, the audience has only seen me dance so far.  I have
seen him doing comedy.   For the
first time I got to play a character which
I had never even thought of.  This
was actually Raj Sir's vision and he said that
you will do this liberation.  And I mean,
my parents might not have trusted me so much.  [laughs]
And to be able to stand with legendary artists like Satish Sir, Anil
Sir,
is a huge thing for us.
Seriously,
come let us sit with you today.  Come on,
what an honor
I am today, all the viewers know that this is
such a family.  All four sisters are
so talented.  [laughter]
Policy, power, liberation and creation.
Yes.  After that father's rhyming ended and
[laughs] the timing is over,
oh ok, speak loudly, Mukti has also become an aunt,
many many congratulations,
oh oh congratulations, a
little baby is born to Neeti, he is very cute,
Golu Molu ji.